creativevideo.co.uk 2007-12-29

# » Creative Video > Creative Video > Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We take privacy issues relating to users of our web sites seriously. We respect your personal information and will hold that information as required by current Data Protection legislation. 

This privacy policy explains what information we will collect about you, how we will use it and the steps we will take to ensure that it is kept secure. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this site, please contact us. By using this web site you consent to us collecting and using personal information about you on the terms set out in this policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back here regularly. 

**What Information We Collect**

Information related to your visit to this site (such as which pages you visit, how often you visit) and the information you supply when becoming a member of creativevideo.co.uk or placing an order online will be held and stored securely by us. Our Data Controller is _creativIDEA_ _Limited_. 

**Cookies**

We currently don't use cookies on creativevideo.co.uk.

**Storage of Sensitive Data**

As we fully respect the privacy of all of our visitors, customers and members, we ensure that our data is stored securely. Using _SmarterStop_ technology, we ensure that any data that is stored, is not accessible by anyone without the proper authorisation. 

**How We Will Use Your Information**

We will use your information to help us improve our web site. We may supply aggregated statistics about the use of our site to third parties such as manufacturers and suppliers, but these statistics will never directly identify you. We will also use your information to keep you informed of _our own_ offers, money off promotions, products or services that we think might interest you. We will never send you messages that promote other third parties & companies. We will never share your information with third parties. By supplying us with your information you confirm that you do not consider use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to be a breach of any of your rights under the Telecommunications (Data Protection and Privacy) Regulations 1999. 

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal details and/or information concerning your activities whilst visiting this site, we shall do so. 

**SPAM**

We are currently aware of professional spammers who use the creativevideo.co.uk domain as the sender. We can assure you that we don't have any involvement in this. Likewise, we have no interest in making you aware of products other than the products that we are proud to sell on this web site. Even so, we **never** send unsolicited emails.

Thank you for taking the time to read our Privacy Policy.

To see the equipment you're interested in before you buy, you are most welcome and indeed encouraged to  
visit us for a few hours to relax and enjoy a dedicated demonstration during which we can address   
any questions you might have and help you to ensure you're investing in the equipment that's right for you.

**Simply call us on 01527 854222 and we'll reserve your place today!**
